Guide to the Gay Cable Network Archives 1982-2001 MSS 231
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XXIX: Lou Maletta and GCN Files
  - GCNTV.com, Undated (Box 173, Folder 30)
  - "Glossary of Video Acronyms", Undated (Box 173, Folder 31)
  - Graphics, Undated (Box 173, Folder 32)
  - Hoffman-LaRoche Inc. - sponsorship proposal, Undated (Box 173, Folder 33)
  - Homo Xtra - The Fetish Issue, vol. 5, no. 32, 1995 (Box 173, Folder 34)
  - Honcho calendar - just the cover, 1980 (Box 173, Folder 35)
  - Human Rights Campaign - magazine, 1996 (Box 173, Folder 36)
  - In Touch for Men - adult calendar, 1980 (Box 173, Folder 37)
  - "Inc Magazine's Guide to Small Business Success", 198738 (Box 173, Folder 38)
  - Inc. article - "Why Bargain Prices Lure Cable Advertisers", 1983 (Box 173, Folder 39)
  - "Incomplete listing of contents in GCN Archive" programs, Undated (Box 173, Folder 40)
  - Independent Gay Health Clubs convention, 1984 (Box 173, Folder 41)
  - "An Interview with Armistead Maupin", Undated (Box 173, Folder 42)
  - Invitations - GCN 10th Anniversary; Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Rights awards; Clinton Inauguration, 1992-1993 (Box 173, Folder 43)
  - J.R.M. Manufacturing - envelope with pictures, Undated (Box 173, Folder 44)
  - Law - Video, Undated (Box 173, Folder 45)
  - Law - Video, Undated (Box 173, Folder 46)
  - Lawyers Alliance for New York, Undated (Box 173, Folder 47)
  - Letters - "To Prospective Producer", 1993-1994 (Box 173, Folder 48)
  - List of Adult Films, Undated (Box 173, Folder 49)
  - List of computer files, Undated (Box 173, Folder 50)
  - Logs - Be Our Guest, 1988-1992 (Box 173, Folder 51)
  - Logs - Candied Camera, Undated (Box 173, Folder 52)
  - Logs - Democratic Convention, 1992 (Box 173, Folder 53)
  - Logs - Democratic Convention, 1996 (Box 173, Folder 54)
  - Logs - Gay USA, 1991 (Box 173, Folder 55)
  - Logs - Gay USA IX, 1991 (Box 173, Folder 56)
  - Logs - Gay USA IX, 9-18, 1991 (Box 173, Folder 57)
  - Logs - Gay USA, 1992 (Box 173, Folder 58)
  - Logs - Gay USA X, 1992 (Box 173, Folder 59)
  - Logs - Gay USA, 1993 (Box 173, Folder 60)
  - Logs - Gay USA XI, 1993 (Box 173, Folder 61)
  - Logs - Gay USA, 1994 (Box 173, Folder 62)
  - Logs - Gay USA XII, 1994 (Box 173, Folder 63)
  - Logs - Gay USA, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Logs - Gay USA XIII, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Logs - Gay USA, 1996 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Logs - Gay USA XIV, 1996 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Logs - Gay USA, 1997 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - Logs - Gay USA XV, 1997 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - Logs - Gay USA XVI, 1997 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - Logs - Gay USA, 1998 (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - Logs - Gay USA XVII, 1998 (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - Logs - Gay USA, 1999 (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - Logs - Gay USA, 2000 (Box 174, Folder 11)
  - Logs - Gay USA, 2000 (Box 174, Folder 12)
  - Logs - Gay USA, 2001 (Box 174, Folder 13)
  - Logs - Gay USA, 2001 (Box 174, Folder 14)
  - Logs - Gay USA - backlog, 2001 (Box 174, Folder 15)
  - Logs - Men & Films, Undated (Box 174, Folder 16)
  - Logs - Men & Films, Undated (Box 174, Folder 17)
  - Logs - Men & Films I, 1983 (Box 174, Folder 18)
  - Logs - Men & Films IV, 1986 (Box 174, Folder 19)
  - Logs - Men & Films V, 1987 (Box 174, Folder 20)
  - Logs - Men & Films VI, 1988 (Box 174, Folder 21)
  - Logs - Men & Films VII, 1989 (Box 174, Folder 22)
  - Logs - Men & Films, 1989-1991 (Box 174, Folder 23)
  - Logs - Men & Films VIII, 1990 (Box 174, Folder 24)
  - Logs - Men & Films X, 1992 (Box 174, Folder 25)
  - Logs - Men & Films XI, 1993 (Box 174, Folder 26)
  - Logs - Men & Films XII, 1994 (Box 174, Folder 27)
  - Logs - Men & Films XIII, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 28)
  - Logs - Men & Films (Gay Pleasure), 1996 (Box 174, Folder 29)
  - Logs - Men & Films XV, 1997 (Box 174, Folder 30)
  - Logs - Men & Films (Houston), 1996 (Box 174, Folder 31)
  - Logs - mixed, Undated (Box 174, Folder 32)
  - Logs - Night of 1000 Gowns, Undated (Box 174, Folder 33)
  - Logs - Pride Parade, 2001 (Box 174, Folder 34)
  - Logs - Pride & Progress, The Right Stuff, Men & Films, Undated (Box 174, Folder 35)
  - Logs - PSA's, Undated (Box 174, Folder 36)
  - Logs - Static, Undated (Box 174, Folder 37)
  - Logs - Stonewall Place After Dark, 1993 (Box 174, Folder 38)
  - Logs / Notes, Undated (Box 174, Folder 39)
  - Logs / Notes - unknown program, Undated (Box 174, Folder 40)
  - Lou Maletta - internet media, 2006 (Box 174, Folder 41)
  - Lou Maletta photography card, Undated (Box 174, Folder 42)
  - "Lou Maletta Photography" layout, Undated (Box 174, Folder 43)
  - "Mannespielen - a portfolio of drawings by Rex", 1975 (Box 174, Folder 44)
  - "Master's Degree" vol.1, no.1, Undated (Box 174, Folder 45)
  - Men & Films, Undated (Box 174, Folder 46)
  - Men & Films - ads, Undated (Box 174, Folder 47)
  - Men & Films - ads, demographics, Undated (Box 174, Folder 48)
  - Men & Films - articles about Woodstock controversy, 1983 (Box 174, Folder 49)
  - Men & Films - catalogs, articles, correspondence, etc. (1 of 2), Undated (Box 174, Folder 50)
  - Men & Films - catalogs, articles, correspondence, etc. (2 of 2), Undated (Box 174, Folder 51)
  - Men & Films - "Clearly a Group Interested in Entertainment", Undated (Box 174, Folder 52)
  - Men & Films - flyer (from frame), Undated (Box 174, Folder 53)
  - Men & Films - In the Dungeon, Undated (Box 174, Folder 54)
  - Men & Films - media package, Undated (Box 174, Folder 55)
  - Men & Films - press, Undated (Box 174, Folder 56)
  - Men & Films - press releases, 1982-1983 (Box 174, Folder 57)
  - Men & Films - porn write-ups, Undated (Box 174, Folder 58)
  - "Men of Manhattah" VHS cover, Undated (Box 174, Folder 59)
  - Michael's Things, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 60)
  - Mid-Atlantic Leather, 2000 (Box 174, Folder 61)
  - Mission Statement - Archives project, Undated (Box 174, Folder 62)
  - NYC Comptroller Commendation, 1992 (Box 174, Folder 63)
  - NYC Pride Guide, 2005 (Box 174, Folder 64)
  - New York Magazine - with pieces of Calvin Klein article cut out, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 65)
  - New York Times - "Supreme Court Roundup", Undated (Box 174, Folder 66)
  - News Clippings - Woodstock, Undated (Box 174, Folder 67)
  - Next, #13.21, 2005 (Box 174, Folder 68)
  - Non-Profit Startup - CRE, Undated (Box 174, Folder 69)
  - Notes and fragments, Undated (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Nova TBC - warranty and manual, Undated (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Nude pictures, Undated (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - Out on Wednesday, 1994 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Paper Magazine, 1997 (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - Party Journal, Undated (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - Passport paper and envelope selector, Undated (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - Petrified Film, Inc. - stock footage list, Undated (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - Phillip Morris [sponsorship], Undated (Box 175, Folder 9)
  - Phillip Morris sponsorship proposal for 1992 Presidential campaign coverage, 1991 (Box 175, Folder 10)
  - "Photo File" - magazine and newspaper clippings, Undated (Box 175, Folder 11)
  - Photos (paper prints) of demonstrations and politicians, Undated (Box 175, Folder 12)
  - Press coverage of GCN shows, Undated (Box 175, Folder 13)
  - Press Pass info, 1999 (Box 175, Folder 14)
  - Press Passes, 1984; 1988 (Box 175, Folder 15)
  - Pride Channel Network - business plan, 1995 (Box 175, Folder 16)
  - Production lists, Undated (Box 175, Folder 17)
  - Program catalog, 1982 (Box 175, Folder 18)
  - Program catalogs - Men & Films, Pride & Progress, Right Stuff, 1982 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Program lists, Undated (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Public Access Television Policy and Procedure Guide, 1993 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Public Relations, 1989 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - P.R. Masters, Undated (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Recent Applicants, Undated (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - Release Forms, Undated (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - Ringling Bros. & Barnum and Bailey - presented by Gay Men's Health Crisis, Inc., 1983 (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - "A Special Opportunity for First Time Advertisers", Undated (Box 176, Folder 9)
  - Staff Training; Center for Lesbian and Gay Studies, CUNY, Undated (Box 176, Folder 10)
  - Stallion, 1982 (Box 176, Folder 11)
  - Tape Inventory, Undated (Box 176, Folder 12)
  - "Television Operational Measurements", Undated (Box 176, Folder 13)
  - Top Man, 1980 (Box 176, Folder 14)
  - Top Man - Men & Films, 1982 (Box 176, Folder 15)
  - Tucson Women's Video Festival flyer, 1984 (Box 176, Folder 16)
  - Vacu-tech - brochure original, Undated (Box 176, Folder 17)
  - Verizon bill, 2007 (Box 176, Folder 18)
  - "Video" chapter in unidentified book, Undated (Box 176, Folder 19)
  - Video course, Undated (Box 176, Folder 20)
  - Video description and cover - "Slave's Revenge", "Rural Raunch", Undated (Box 176, Folder 21)
  - Video list, Undated (Box 176, Folder 22)
  - Videomaster's Preliminary Production Checklist (FACL), 1981 (Box 176, Folder 23)
  - The Village Voice - "The Cable Rednecks", 1983 (Box 176, Folder 24)
  - "Whoop-Dee-Doo" - magazine and newspaper clippings, Undated (Box 176, Folder 25)
  - Woodstock Access TV Times, 1983 (Box 176, Folder 26)
- Oversize Series XXIX: Lou Maletta and GCN Files
  This series contains the oversize paper materials from the Lou Maletta and GCN files series.
  - Subseries A: Files
    - 32 Union Sq. East - address cards - originals, Undated (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - The Advocate - "Gay TV on Yasgur's Farm" - mounted article, issue 363, Undated (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Arcos Blancos: San Juan's Premiere Guest House - print, Undated (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - DARE newsletter - vol.1, no. 27, 1988 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Donna Summer - "She Works Hard for the Money" full page ad - Billboard, 1983 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - FACIT - letterhead original, Undated (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Gay USA - Achievement Award from ICAN - "Best Network Original Program", 1991 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - GCN Conventions '88 - flyer originals, Undated (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - GCN - letterhead originals, Undated (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - GCN / Lou Maletta business cards - original, Undated (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - GCN - party invitation master, Undated (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Hong Kong Men - 1996 Calendar (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - "Le Gai Pied" poster, Undated (Box 177, Folder 13)
    - Louis P. Maletta - letterhead original, Undated (Box 177, Folder 14)
    - Lou Maletta Photography - logo original, Undated (Box 177, Folder 15)
    - Luke P. Valenti - letterhead original, Undated (Box 177, Folder 16)
    - Men & Films - business cards original, Undated (Box 177, Folder 17)
    - Men & Films - flyer originals, Undated (Box 177, Folder 18)
    - Men & Films - letterhead original, Undated (Box 177, Folder 19)
    - Men & Films - promo print, Undated (Box 177, Folder 20)
    - Men of Manhattan - mailers original, Undated (Box 177, Folder 21)
    - Model release form - original, Undated (Box 177, Folder 22)
    - "The Monster" poster - original, Undated (Box 177, Folder 23)
    - Night of a Thousand Gowns - videotape cover original, 1987 (Box 177, Folder 24)
    - Note from Emma, Undated (Box 177, Folder 25)
    - Photograph - portrait of Lou Maletta, 1987 (Box 177, Folder 26)
    - Photographs - protest in the U.K., 1988 (Box 177, Folder 27)
    - Rate cards - originals, Undated (Box 177, Folder 28)
    - Videotape order form - original, Undated (Box 177, Folder 29)
  - Subseries B: Periodicals
    - The Advocate, no. 361, 364, 1983 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - The Connections - vol. 2, no. 7, 8, 11, 1983 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - The Connection - vol. 2, no. 22, 1983 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - The Dallas Downtown News - vol. 7, no. 44, 1984 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - The Dallas Morning News - Convention '84, 1984 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Dallas Voice - vol. 1, no. 15, 1984 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Dollars & Sense - vol. 13, no. 8, 1982 (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Life Magazine, 1971 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - The Medical Herald - vol. 17, no. 11, 2005 (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Mixed newspaper clippings, 1978; 1983-1984 (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - Multichannel News - vol. 5, no. 50, 1984 (Box 178, Folder 11)
    - New York Blade, 2002-2003 (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - New York Blade, 2003-2004 (Box 178, Folder 13)
    - The New York City News, 1983 (Box 178, Folder 14)
    - The National Law Journal, 1985 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - New York Press - vol. 17, no. 39, 2004 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - San Jose Mercury News - convention edition, 1984 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - The Spiritual Herald - vol. 4, no. 11, 2005 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Stonewall News - no. 72, 1994 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Sunday Record, 1983 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - The Vault, 1995 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - The Village Voice, 1983; 2008 (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - The Weekly News, 1986 (Box 179, Folder 9)
    - Wire, no. 20, 1995 (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - The Woodstock Times - vol. 12, no. 8, 9, 10, 1983 (Box 179, Folder 11)
    - The Woodstock Times - vol. 12, no. 13, 15, 1983 (Box 179, Folder 12)
    - Ulster County Townsman - vol. XXX, no. 8-10, 14, 1983 (Box 179, Folder 13)
- Series XXX: Photographs
  This series contains all of the photographs, slides, and negatives from the GCN files.
  - Mixed photographs, including GCN staff, protests, and pornography., Undated (Binder A)
- Series XXXI: Objects
  This series contains objects kept by Lou Maletta and GCN.
  - Purple T-shirt with GCN logo on back, Undated (Box 181, Object ID: 231.2.0003)
  - Purple T-shirt with GCN logo on front, Undated (Box 181, Object ID: 231.2.0004)
    There are two copies of this shirt, one of which has had the sleeves cut off.
  - Tye-dye T-shirt from Conventions '88 with several GCN logos, 1988 (Box 182, Object ID: 231.2.0005)
    There are six copies of this shirt, one of which has had the collar cut off.
- Oversize Series XXXI: Objects
  - Marble plaque - "Accept Differences, Be Kind...", 2003 (Box 180, Object ID: 231.2.0001)
  - Wooden camera with "GCN" on front, Undated (Box 180, Object ID: 231.2.0002)